ILGWU. Charles Zimmerman Collection of Radical Pamphlets 5780/178
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Israel returns to history: a chapter in the fight for Israel, November 1945-July 1948., 1949 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America. Charges: what they constitute and how to handle them (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Stuart Chase. The tragedy of waste, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  In conjunction with the Labor Bureau, incorporated
- Christianity on the Nazi cross., 1936 (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Education Department. The Church and unionism: some pronouncements of Church spokesmen on labor organization and collective bargaining / issued by Educational Department, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Anton Ciliga. The Kronstadt revolt, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 98)
- C. I. O.: promise or menace?, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 99)
- CIO resolutions on social welfare: CIO 11th Constitutional Convention, Cleveland, Ohio, October 31-November 4, 1949. (Box 2, Folder 100)
- CIO Committee to Abolish Discrimination. C.I.O. wants F.E.P.C., 1949 (Box 2, Folder 101)
- The C. I. O.; what it is and how it came to be; a brief history of the Committee for Industrial Organization., 1937 (Box 2, Folder 102)
- CIO's victory program: win-the-war policies and actions adopted at the Vth CIO Convention, Boston, Mass., November, 1942. (Box 2, Folder 103)
- Walter Citrine. The T.U.C. in war-time, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 104)
- NAACP. Civil rights at Mid-Century: NAACP annual report, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 105)
- American Jewish Congress. Civil rights in the United States: a balance sheet of group relations, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 106)
- The CIO what it is and what it does, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 107)
- Louis Colman. Lawrence Simpson's "Treason", 1936 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- August Claessens; Rebecca E. Jarvis. A B C of parliamentary law, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  A brief handbook on rules of order for meetings adapted to the needs of labor groups and an appendix of charts, tables, examples, etc.
- August Claessens. The blue eagle is dead, so what?, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- August Claessens. Eugene Victor Debs: a tribute, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  With excerpts from some of Debs speeches.
- August Claessens. Race prejudice; a description of the various factors in racial animosities, discriminations, and conflicts, and the conditions under which these antagonisms are increased or eliminated., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- August Claessens. What organized labor wants: a popular description of trade union philosophy, economics and ideals, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Matthew E. Clancy. The sound old guilds, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- National Consumers' League. Clarifying the Constitution by amendment, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Addresses made at the thirty-seventh annual meeting of the National Consumers' League, New York City, December 15, 1936.
- Lindley D. Clark. Labor laws that have been declared unconstitutional, 1922 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  November, 1922
- J. X. Cohen. Helping to end economic discrimination: second report on Jewish non-employment, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Class struggle, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  v.3:no.1-3 (1919:Feb.-Aug.)
- Class struggle, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  v.4:no.1 (1934:Jan.)
- J. X. Cohen. The negro, the Jew and the FEPC, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- J. X. Cohen. Towards fair play for Jewish workers: third report on Jewish non-employment, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Eleanor G. Coit. Government support of workers' education, with special reference to a study of the relation of private and public agencies in the field of workers' education in Denmark and Sweden, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- M. J. Coldwell. Canadian progressives on the march: the story of the rise of the C.C.F., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Regina Manifesto; post-war program.
- The Communist, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  v.6:no.2, 5-7
- The Communist, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  v.7:no.1-5
- The Communist, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  v.7:no.6-8, 10, 12
- The Communist, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  v.8:no.1, 3-4, 6-8, 10
- The Communist, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  v.9:no.1, 10
- The Communist, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  v.10:no.1-6, 8
- The Communist, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  v.11:no.6, 12
- The Communist, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  v.12:no.3, 5
- The Communist, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  v.13:no.6, 9-11
- The Communist, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  v.14:no.3, 6, 11
- The Communist, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  v.15:no.11
- The Communist, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  v.16:no.3, 10
- The Communist, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  v.17:no.9
- Commercial handbook of the U.S.S.R., 1927 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Commonwealth Federarion of New York. The Commonwealth Federation: economic program and plan of action (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Communist international. Communism and the international situation: thesis on the international situation and the tasks of the Communist International, adopted at the Sixth World Congress of the Communist International, 1928, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Communist Anti-Semitism, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  Report made to the Jewish Labor Committee annual conference, Atlantic City, April 17-18th, 1953.
- National Campaign Committee of the Communist Party. The Communist election platform, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- National Committee of the Communist Party. Communist election platform 1938: for jobs, security, democracy and peace (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Communist Party of the U.S.A. Communist election program against hunger, wage cuts, speed-up and war: New York elections, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Andrew Avery. The communist fifth column: what's the truth about it-- and what isn't., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- The Communist international, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  v.7:no.11(1935). Should be v.12:no.11(1935) typographical error on title page.
- The Communist international, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  v.12:no.7, 14(1935)
- The Communist international, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  v.13:no.1-3, 5-7(1936)
- The Communist international, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  v.14:no.11-12(1937)
- The Communist international (Box 3, Folder 42)
  Jubilee no.1
- Labour Party (Great Britain). The Communist Party and affiliation: notes for speakers, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- The Communist review, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  v.3:no.12 (1923:April)
- The Communist review, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  v.4:no.1-3 (1923:May-July)
- The Communist review, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  v.1:no.11 (1929:Nov.)
- Publications Committee, Warehouse and Distribution Workers Union, Local 688, International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Community meetings: a new approach to trade union political action; a grass-roots experiment conducted by Teamsters Local 688, St. Louis, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Communist Party of the U.S.A. The constitution and by-laws of the Communist party of the United States of America, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Charles E. Ruthenberg; Isaac E. Ferguson. A communist trial: extracts from the testimony of C.E. Ruthenberg and closing address to the jury by Isaac E. Ferguson. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- United Transport Service Employees of America. Congress!: close the gap; the case of sub-standard wages, among Red caps, Dining Car employees and Pullman Laundry workers, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America. Constitution and by-laws of the Seafarers' International Union of North America, Atlantic and Gulf District., 1938 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Herbert Benjamin. Constitution and regulations of the National Unemployment Council of the U. S. A., 1934 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- New York State Federation of Labor. Constitution: rules of order and declaration of purposes of the New York State Federation of Labor., 1898 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Constitution (fundamental law) of the Union of soviet socialist republics, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Italian-American Labor Council. A contribution to America's victory and the Italy's freedom, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Rufus Cornelsen. Pastor goes to CIO Convention (Box 4, Folder 14)
- David Coyle. Economic freedom for America, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Ryland Wesley Crary; Gerald L. Steibel. How you can teach about communism, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Union for Democratic Socialism. Creeping socialism? (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Communist Party of the U.S.A. The Crisis in the Communist Party, U. S. A., 1930 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  2 copies
- John F. Cronin. Prices in the United States, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- John F. Cronin. Rugged individualism, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Frank Rudolph Crosswaith; Alfred Baker Lewis. Discrimination, incorporated, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Nelson H. Cruikshank. Your stake in the social security trust fund, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- League of Professional Groups for Foster and Ford. Culture and the crisis: an open letter to the writers, artists, teachers, physicians, engineers, scientists and other professional workers of America., 1932 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Joseph Curran. Know the score: on Seamen's conditions before the NMU, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Joseph Curran. The membership wins again: a record of recent events in the National Maritime Unio, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Helen Dallas. Chain stores: pro and con, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Karl Dannenberg. Karl Marx, the man and his work, and The constructive elements of socialism; three lectures and two essays, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- S. R. Mohan Das. Ho Chi Minh, nationalist or Soviet agent?, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Maurice R. Davie. What shall we do about immigration?, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- John A. Davis. How management can integrate Negroes in war industries, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- John P. Davis. Let us build a national Negro congress, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Saville R. Davis. Italy under the swastika (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Communist Party of the U.S.A. Day of solidarity and unity in struggle, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Vera Micheles Dean. After victory Questions and answers on world organization., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Vera Micheles Dean. On the threshold of world order, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Congress of Jewish Culture. A decade of destruction: Jewish culture in the USSR, 1948-1958. (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Liberal Party of New York State. Liberal Party: declaration and platform, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Workers Party of the U.S.. Declaration of principles and constitution of the Workers Party of the U.S., 1934 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Defend democracy. Communist activities examined. (Box 4, Folder 39)
  Two statements of policy by the Trades Union Congress General Council.
- Daniel De Leon. Socialist reconstruction of society: the industrial vote, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Democracy and civil liberties. A list of the resolutions, actions, and official declarations of The American Federation of Labor on democracy and civil liberties from 1881-1938. (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Committee on Democracy in Trade Unions.. Democracy in trade unions, Supplement, with desirable provisions from trade union by-laws, and references to court cases indicated in the report., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Leon Dennen. The Soviet peace myth, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Eugene Dennis. Is communism unamerican? Nine questions about the Communist Party answered, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Eugene Dennis. The Elections and the outlook for national unity, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Eugene Dennis. I challenge the un-Americans, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Eugene Dennis. Let the people know the truth about the Communists which the un-American committee tried to suppress, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Der Weg zum sozialistischen Deutschland (Box 4, Folder 48)
  German
- Richard L.G. Deverall. 38th parallel, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Richard L.G. Deverall. Hara kiri! Occupied Japan's trade with Soviet China, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Richard L.G. Deverall. Japan's Soviet held prisoners of war, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Richard L.G. Deverall. Soviet imperialism: highest stage of communism., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Dialectics; a Marxist literary journal., 1937 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Milton Diamond. Petrillo's case: new light on an age-old problem: man vs. machine, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- P. R. Dietrich. Towards the world October: the fourteenth anniversary of the Russian (Bolshevik) October revolution, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Georgi Dimitrov. To defend assassins is to help fascism, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Georgi Dimitrov. The united front against fascism and war, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Georgi Dimitrov. The united struggle for peace, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Georgi Dimitrov. Working class unity. Bulwark against fascism: the fascist offensive and the tasks of the Communist International in the fight for the unity of the working class against fascism., 1935 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Aaron Director. Unemployment, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  Reading with a Purpose no. 66
- Do citizens and education mix? A community guide to school study. The Connecticut report: community studies., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Joe Doakes. I know my neighbors, do you? (Box 4, Folder 62)
- New York Times. Documents on world security, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Mary Honor Donlon. Looking ahead in New York State workmen's compensation, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Dr. Chaim Zhitlowsky: his life and writings (biographical sketch), 1935 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Draft for a program for the Socialist Party, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  Formulated by the Left Wing at the Socialist Call Institutes, Bound Brook, N.J., Sept. 7-8, Chicago, Ill., Oct. 19-20.
- Robert W. Dunn. Company unions today, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Robert W. Dunn. Spying on workers, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  2nd edition
- Robert W. Dunn. What war means to the workers: answering the question, will war bring back prosperity?, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  Revised edition
- William F. Dunne. Why Hearst lies about communism: three open letters to William Randolph Hearst, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 70)
- R. Palme Dutt. The two Internationals, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- Max Eastman. The trial of Eugene Debs: with Debs' address to the court on receiving sentence, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 72)
- National Committee on Immigration Policy. Economic aspects of immigration, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 73)
- Marion Edman; Laurentine B. Collins. Promising practices in intergroup education, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  Prepared for administrative Committee on Intercultural Education, Detroit Public Schools
- Henryk Ehrlich; Haim Kantorovitch; Anna Bercowitz.. The struggle for revolutionary socialism, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  translated by Haim Kantorovitch and Anna Bercowitz.
- Ellis. Oil on the flames (Box 4, Folder 76)
  advertisement about a speech
- National Community Relations Advisory Council.. Equality of opportunity in housing, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 77)
- League of Struggle for Negro Rights. Equality, land and freedom: a program for Negro liberation, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  Draft submitted by the National Council of the League of Struggle for Negro Rights.
- Abraham Epstein. Social security, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 79)
- Palmiro Togliatti. The fight for peace, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  Report on the preparations for imperialist war and the tasks of the Communist International, delivered August 13, 1935
- Anna Damon. Ernst Thaelmann, fighter against war and fascism, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 81)
- M. K. Eroshkin. The soviets in Russia, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  Mir, zemstvo and soviet. The bolshevist economic policy. The land problem in Russia. The labor problem in Russia.
- Socialist Party. Evaluation of the Meeting of the National Executive Committee, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  Buffalo, March 22-24, 1935
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations). Everybody's business: World plans for peace and security., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 84)
- American Jewish tercentenary, 1654-1954, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 85)
- Evidence on the reign of racialism in Czechoslovakia, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 86)
- Expel the traitor! Kick out Jim Crow!, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 87)
- Lincoln Eyre. Russia Analyzed, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 88)
- Bela Fabian. Hungary's Jewry faces liquidation, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 89)
- Labour Party (Great Britain). Facing the facts; an interim statement of Labour's home policy., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 90)
- James T. Farrell. Truth and myth about America, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  A statement against dictatorship of or over the proletariat, and offering a democratic change for social progress.
- General Jewish Council. Father Coughlin, his "facts" and arguments, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 92)
- I. F. (Isidor F.) Stone. The Court disposes, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 93)
- Festival Bailable (Box 4, Folder 94)
- B. J. Field. Prospects of American capitalism (Box 4, Folder 95)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). Fifty years of service, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  Report of the Executive Council to the 1931 Convention meeting in Vancouver, B.C., Canada, contained an audit of the stewardship of the American Federation of Labor, closing fifty years of activity and leadership
- Fight! Don't starve! Organize: demands for unemployment insurance made upon the United State Congress., 1931 (Box 4, Folder 97)
- Jane Filley; Therese Mitchell. Consider the Laundry Workers, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 98)
- Ernst Fischer. For or against the united front?, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 99)
- Geraldine Townsend Fitch. China lob-lolly (Box 4, Folder 100)
- Gerald C. Treacy. Five great encyclicals: labor, education, marriage, reconstructing the social order, atheistic communism, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  With Discussion Club outlines by Gerald C. Treacy
- Elizabeth Gurley Flynn. I didn't raise my boy to be a soldier for Wall Street, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- John T. Flynn. Recovery through war scares, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Friedrich Wilhelm Foerster; T. H. Tetens. Open letter to the "Loyal Americans of German descent", 1943 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Food for thought, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  v.10:no.1 (1949:Oct.)
- Fools and cowards cut their own throats (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Communist Party of the U.S.A. For a communist party of action, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Against liquidating the Workers (Communist) Party. Against substituting the Workers (Communist) Party by a sham Farmer-Labor Party. An appeal to the members of district no. 2, Workers Party
- John Pepper. For a labor party. Recent revolutionary changes in American politics, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Communist Party of the U.S.A. For a powerful united A.F. of L., 1936 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Communist Party USA (Opposition). For unity of the world Communist movement, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  A letter to the Independent Labor Party of Great Britain from the Communist Party USA (Opposition).
- Federal Security Agency. For you and yours, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- William Trufant Foster. Loan sharks and their victims, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- William Z. Foster. Beware of the war danger! Stop, look and listen!, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- William Z. Foster. Communism versus fascism, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- William Z. Foster. The crisis in the Socialist party, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- William Z. Foster. Industrial unionism, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- William Z. Foster. Little brothers of the big labor fakers, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Report of a speech against the Conference For Progressive Labor Action, made in New Star Casino, New York City, on May 10, 1931
- William Z. Foster. The railroaders' next step: amalgamation, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- William Z. Foster. The revolutionary crisis of 1918-1921: in Germany, England, Italy and France (Box 5, Folder 19)
- William Z. Foster; Earl Browder; V. M. Molotov. Technocracy and Marxism; The Technical Intelligentsia and Socialist Construction, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- William Z. Foster. Toward soviet America, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- William Z. Foster. Unionizing steel, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- William Z. Foster. What means a strike in steel, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- William Z. Foster. Workers, Defend Your Unions!, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Political Action Committee. Four men speak about jobs for all, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Communist International. Fourth congress of the Communist International, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Abridged report of meetings held at Petrograd & Moscow, Nov. 7-Dec. 3, 1922.
- United States. Advisory Commission on Educational Exchange. Fourth semiannual report on educational exchange activities, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Letter from the Chairman, the United States Advisory Commission on Educational Exchange, Department of State.
- Jay Fox. Amalgamation, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Trades Union Congress. Free trade unions form the I.C.F.T.U., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Joseph Freeman. The background of German fascism, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Freemasons and Spain: struggle of Masonic liberalism against reactionism in Spain., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Olivia P. Frost. An analysis of the characteristics of the population in Central Harlem, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Varian Fry. The peace that failed; how Europe sowed the seeds of war, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Fundamentals of Communism, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Joseph Gaer. Let our people live: a plea for a living wage, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Romulo Gallegos. Reconocer es no conocer (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Walter Galenson. Some aspects of industrial relations in Denmark (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Harry Gannes. How the Soviet Union Helps Spain, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Sander Genis. The menace of Nazism and Fascism, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  By Sander Genis, Manager Twin City Joint Board, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America.
- Aaron Gertz. The social structure of Jewish settlement in Palestine, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Americo Ghioldi. La situacion economica, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Francis James Gilligan. Negro workers in free America, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Benjamin Gitlow. Some plain words on Communist unity, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Kate Gitlow. Women in politics (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Katherine Glover. Women at Work in Wartime, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Michael Gold. The damned agitator and other stories (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Samuel Gompers. The American labor movement; its makeup, achievements and aspirations, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Samuel Gompers. The voluntary basis of trade unionism, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  Memorial edition
- Samuel Gompers Centennial Committee. Gompers evaluated (Box 5, Folder 49)
  A collection of articles about Samuel Gompers' philosophy and career written a generation ago by prominent journalists and historians.
- Samuel Gompers Centennial Committee. Gompers heritage, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  Addresses delivered during the centennial of Samuel Gompers' birth.
- Ceferino Gonzalez. La rebellion militaire en Espagne et l'incomprehension des democraties europeennes devant un aussi grave probleme, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Maksim Gorky. To American intellectuals, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Francis J. Gorman. The fate of trade unions under fascism, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Edith Gosling. Ticktock: a reading text for English classes (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Klement Gottwald. The united front in Czechoslovakia, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Democratic National Committee. Governor Landon vs. Candidate Landon, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- NLRB (National Labor Relations Board). Governmental protection of labor's right to organize, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  Summary of evidence introduced at a hearing before the National labor relations board bearing upon the factual basis of the National labor relations act and the reasonableness of the regulations embodied therein.
- Gil Green. The truth about Soviet Russia, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Gil Green. United we stand for peace and socialism, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Gil Green. Young Communists and unity of the youth, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- William Green. Address delivered by William Green, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- William Green. A Democratic Institution, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- William Green. Remove the barriers (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Hayim Greenberg. To a communist friend (Box 5, Folder 64)